<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?>
<rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom">
  <channel>
    <title>Neha Hudait</title>
    <link>nhudait.github.io/</link>
    <description>Recent content on Neha Hudait</description>
    <generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator>
    <language>en-us</language><atom:link href="nhudait.github.io/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml" />
    <item>
      <title>Software Engineering Intern | NVIDIA</title>
      <link>nhudait.github.io/nvidia/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2017 03:29:08 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>nhudait.github.io/nvidia/</guid>
      <description>Coming Soon! </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Unit Supervisor | Student Technology Services</title>
      <link>nhudait.github.io/sts/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2017 03:29:08 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>nhudait.github.io/sts/</guid>
      <description>Overview Through Student Technology Services, I am currently a Unit Supervisor where I oversee a team of 5-8 Student Technology Consultants (STCs) who provide frontline technical support for over 40,000 students. I am also responsible for maintaining Unit 1&amp;rsquo;s Academic Center hardware, software, and printing services.
Previously, I was a Student Technology Consultant where I continually assisted the student body in troubleshooting their software and hardware related issues. Additionally, I participated in trainings and professional development.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title></title>
      <link>nhudait.github.io/ieee/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2017 03:29:08 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>nhudait.github.io/ieee/</guid>
      <description>Overview IEEE has been one of the most influential organizations I have joined in college. I joined IEEE my freshman year as a Professional Development committee member where I planned professional development workshops for IEEE members. Flash forward, I became Professional Development committee director and now am External Vice President of the organization!
As External Vice President, I primarily work with the external facing committees that affect IEEE&amp;rsquo;s image. More specifically, I primarily work with the website, industry relations, and outreach committees.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Technical Product Manager | Division of Data Science</title>
      <link>nhudait.github.io/data/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2017 03:29:08 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>nhudait.github.io/data/</guid>
      <description>Coming Soon! </description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Advisor &#43; Co-Founder | DataGood</title>
      <link>nhudait.github.io/datagood/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2017 03:29:08 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>nhudait.github.io/datagood/</guid>
      <description>Overview Coming soon!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Technical Product Management | SAP Ariba</title>
      <link>nhudait.github.io/sap/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2017 03:29:08 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>nhudait.github.io/sap/</guid>
      <description>Overview During my internship at SAP, I worked with the Platform Search team on the deployment of Search 3.0, a search engine used to streamline sourcing and procurement options for small businesses that use SAP&amp;rsquo;s SAAS platforms. This was my first taste of a B2B company and what it was like to deploy a product and instantaneously get feedback from consumers.
More specifically, I developed Key Performance Indicators to understand externally, how well the search platform was doing in aiding customers.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Software Developer | Girl Effect</title>
      <link>nhudait.github.io/girleffect/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2017 03:29:08 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>nhudait.github.io/girleffect/</guid>
      <description>Overview Girl Effect is a nonprofit organization dedicated to empowering and educating girls across the world, especially in developing countries, through Artificial Intelligence. I worked as a Software Developer for Girl Effect on their conversational AI products aimed to answer questions from girls. More specifically, I worked on Big Sis and Chhaa Jaa, Girl Effect&amp;rsquo;s flagship products in the United States and India.
My work was primarily centered around improving the chatbot&amp;rsquo;s functionality in understanding what the intent of the girl&amp;rsquo;s message is and delivering tailored results.</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Machine Learning Developer | University of California San Francisco Medical Center</title>
      <link>nhudait.github.io/ucsf/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2017 03:29:08 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>nhudait.github.io/ucsf/</guid>
      <description>Overview Coming Soon!
Workflow Coming Soon!
Takeaways Coming Soon!</description>
    </item>
    
    <item>
      <title>Data Analyst | Goldman School of Public Policy</title>
      <link>nhudait.github.io/environment/</link>
      <pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2017 03:29:08 -0700</pubDate>
      
      <guid>nhudait.github.io/environment/</guid>
      <description>Overview Coming Soon!
Workflow Coming Soon!
Takeaways Coming Soon!</description>
    </item>
    
  </channel>
</rss>
