<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Experiences on Neha Hudait</title><link>https://nhudait.github.io/experience/</link><description>Recent content in Experiences on Neha Hudait</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><lastBuildDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2017 03:29:08 -0700</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://nhudait.github.io/experience/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Technical Program Manager Intern | NVIDIA</title><link>https://nhudait.github.io/experience/nvidiatpm/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2017 03:29:08 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://nhudait.github.io/experience/nvidiatpm/</guid><description>Coming Soon!</description></item><item><title>Software Engineering Intern | Meta</title><link>https://nhudait.github.io/experience/facebook/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2017 03:29:08 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://nhudait.github.io/experience/facebook/</guid><description>Overview During my internship at Facebook, I worked on the People Data Privacy team to design and develop a machine learning system and baseline model to detect 20,000 privacy violations with 99.4% accuracy. Facebook has several commitments to suspend the collection of device-related data collected on its services or third-party websites without the consent of users. PDP Privacy is part of a larger initiative to detect and prevent these privacy violations in an effort to improve overall privacy of Facebook&amp;rsquo;s Family of Apps.</description></item><item><title>Software Engineering Intern | NVIDIA</title><link>https://nhudait.github.io/experience/nvidia/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2017 03:29:08 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://nhudait.github.io/experience/nvidia/</guid><description>Overview During my internship at NVIDIA, I worked on the Product Security Team to develop a part of Morpheus, a cloud-native cybersecurity framework which uses machine learning to identify, capture, and take action on threats and anomalies that were previously impossible to identify including leaks of unencrypted sensitive data, phishing attacks, and malware. I specifically worked on the user-facing side of this by creating an internal-facing full-stack portal to allow NVIDIA engineers to analyze different security logs from sources like AWS, GCP, Kafka, etc.</description></item><item><title>Software Developer | Girl Effect</title><link>https://nhudait.github.io/experience/girleffect/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2017 03:29:08 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://nhudait.github.io/experience/girleffect/</guid><description>Overview Girl Effect is a nonprofit organization dedicated to empowering and educating girls across the world, especially in developing countries, through Artificial Intelligence. I worked as a Software Developer for Girl Effect on their conversational AI products aimed to answer questions from girls. More specifically, I worked on Big Sis and Chhaa Jaa, Girl Effect&amp;rsquo;s flagship products in the United States and India.
My work was primarily centered around improving the chatbot&amp;rsquo;s functionality in understanding what the intent of the girl&amp;rsquo;s message is and delivering tailored results.</description></item><item><title>Technical Product Manager | Division of Data Science</title><link>https://nhudait.github.io/experience/data/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2017 03:29:08 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://nhudait.github.io/experience/data/</guid><description>Overview I worked with the Infrastructure Team at the Division of Data Science at UC Berkeley to design and develop new features and roadmaps for Otter-Grader, a lightweight, modular open-source autograder. Prior to coming into my role, the team was comprised of 4 developers and a team lead who acted as a psuedo PM. However, becausse of the vast growth of the number of adopters of Otter-Grader, I was brought onboard to analyze key takeaways and to design new features to iterate on future versions of Otter.</description></item><item><title>Technical Product Management | SAP Ariba</title><link>https://nhudait.github.io/experience/sap/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2017 03:29:08 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://nhudait.github.io/experience/sap/</guid><description>Overview During my internship at SAP, I worked with the Platform Search team on the deployment of Search 3.0, a search engine used to streamline sourcing and procurement options for small businesses that use SAP&amp;rsquo;s SAAS platforms. This was my first taste of a B2B company and what it was like to deploy a product and instantaneously get feedback from consumers.
More specifically, I developed Key Performance Indicators to understand externally, how well the search platform was doing in aiding customers.</description></item><item><title>Machine Learning Developer | University of California San Francisco Medical Center</title><link>https://nhudait.github.io/experience/ucsf/</link><pubDate>Sun, 15 Oct 2017 03:29:08 -0700</pubDate><guid>https://nhudait.github.io/experience/ucsf/</guid><description>Overview I worked with the Cardiovascular Department at the University of California San Francisco Medial Center to improve AI-enabled detection and preventuion techniques for cardiovacular disease. Currently, cardiovascular disease can be detected through different ultrasounds. However, there is a high turnaround time between completing the ultrasound, analyzing the video, and determining to what extent of severity the patient has cardiovascular dieases i.e. whether they were at risk, required medication, etc.</description></item></channel></rss>